<persona id='sheen' displayName='Charlie Sheen'>
    
    <!-- quotes for successful builds -->
    <quote type="success">Uh, I'm bi-winning.  I win here, I win there.</quote>
    <quote type="success">Winner winner chicken dinner?  I don't think so.  Winner-winner SHEEN dinner!</quote>
	<quote type="success">I am on a drug. It's called Charlie Sheen. It's not available. If you try it once, you will die.</quote>
	<quote type="success">I was bangin' seven-gram rocks and finishing them because that's how I roll.</quote>
	<quote type="success">I have one speed, one gear: GO!</quote>
	<quote type="success">I have a different constitution. I have a different brain; I have a different heart; I got tiger blood, man</quote>
	<quote type="success">I'm sorry, man, but I've got magic. I've got poetry in my fingertips.</quote>
	<quote type="success">Most of the time - and this includes naps - I'm an F-18, bro. And I will destroy you in the air. I will deploy my ordinance to the ground.</quote>
	<quote type="success">You borrow my brain for 5 seconds and just be like, 'Dude! Can't handle it! Unplug this bastard!' Yeah.</quote>
	<quote type="success">All we do is put wins in the record books.</quote>
	<quote type="success">We win so radically in our underwear before our first cup of coffee, it's scary.</quote>
	<quote type="success">I mean, what's not to love? Especially when you see how I party man, it's epic.</quote>
	<quote type="success">The run I was on made Sinatra, Flynn, Jagger, Richards, all of them, just look like droopy-eyed, armless children.</quote>
	<quote type="success">I'm tired of pretending I'm not a total bitchin' rock star from Mars.</quote>
	<quote type="success">You can't process me with a normal brain.</quote>
	<quote type="success">I am battle-tested bayonets, bro.</quote>
	<quote type="success">I'm not Thomas Jefferson. He was a pussy.</quote>
	<quote type="success">Winning.</quote>
	<quote type="success">C'mon bro, I won best picture at 20. I wasn't even trying. I wasn't even warm.</quote>
	<quote type="success">You have the right to kill me, but you do not have the right to judge me. Boom. That's the whole movie. That's life.</quote>
	<quote type="success">My body is a lock box of diamonds, uranium, and assassin nobility</quote>
	<quote type="success">Warning: The taste of Charlie Sheen has the ability to make your soul weep, and forfeit.</quote>
	<quote type="success">I'm living the life of a rockstar vatican assassin.</quote>
	<quote type="success">Winning, anyone? Rhymes with winning. Anyone? Yeah, that would be us. Sorry, man, didn't make the rules. Oops!</quote>
	<quote type="success">I am battle-tested bayonets, bro.</quote>
	<quote type="success">The only thing I'm addicted to right now is winning.</quote>
	<quote type="success">Like a Dinosaur Stampede from middle earth RAGING atop Col. Kilgore's main rotor, our assault must be EPIC.</quote>
	<quote type="success">It's been a tsunami of media and I've been riding it on a mercury surfboard.</quote>
	<quote type="success">We work for the pope, we murder people. We're Vatican assassins. How complicated can it be?</quote>
	<quote type="success">What they're not ready for is guys like you and I and Nails and all the other gnarly gnarlingtons in my life</quote>
	<quote type="success">We are high priests, Vatican assassin warlocks. Boom. Print that, people.</quote>
	<quote type="success">I blinked and I cured my brain.</quote>
	<quote type="success">I'm grandiose.  Because I live a grandiose life.  I'm not aw shucks.. because I'm gnarly.</quote>
	<quote type="success">I'm celebrating me, every day.</quote>
	<quote type="success">I'm sober down to my Adonis DNA.</quote>
	<quote type="success">the title of my book has finally been delivered thru vast and extensive Lunar channels. "Apocalypse Me" Warlock Latin for WINNING.</quote>
	<quote type="success">psst, check it, you've been warned. #SheensKorner violent torpedo of truth. love or hate. do the math.</quote>
	<quote type="success">fastball. the trolls are foaming from their toothless holes. rumor mill abundant with evil gossip. mainstream heretics smirking.</quote>

    <!-- quotes for failed builds -->
	<quote type="failure">Look what I'm dealing with, man, I'm dealing with fools and trolls.</quote>
	<quote type="failure">Oh wait, can't process it. Losers. Winning. Buh bye.</quote>
    <quote type="failure">Boom, crush. Night, losers. Winning, duh.</quote>
    <quote type="failure">I have defeated this earthworm with my words. Imagine what I would have done with my fire breathing fists.</quote>
	<quote type="failure">There's a storm coming - and it's me.</quote>
	<quote type="failure">And for those that are not onboard, it's like, 'Catch ya in the rearview, losers.'</quote>
	<quote type="failure">This Warlock is in the breach. Poised. T-minus 51 mins. read my tigerblood dripping lips; you've been warned.</quote>
	<quote type="failure">I live inside the truth, and you cannot debate me.</quote>
	<quote type="failure">Dying is for fools, amateurs.</quote>
	<quote type="failure">I'm not fair game. I'm not a soft target. It's over. There's a new sheriff in town. And he has an army of assassins.</quote>
	<quote type="failure">Can't is the cancer of happening.</quote>	
</persona>
